dillards.com 2017-12-28

# FAQ - US and International | Dillards.com

## Company Notices & Terms of Use

### California Transparency in Supply Chains Act

California Transparency in Supply Chain Act Statement 2010

The following describes Dillard's efforts to eradicate slavery and human trafficking from its direct supply chains. Among other measures, Dillard's:

  1. Engages in verification of product supply chains for products imported by Dillard's to evaluate and address risks of human trafficking and slavery. See [Dillard's Social Accountability Policy](https://investor.shareholder.com/dillards/documentdisplay.cfm?DocumentID=3150) and [Dillard's Social Accountability Report](https://investor.shareholder.com/dillards/documentdisplay.cfm?DocumentID=6458) for details. Dillard's utilizes third party inspectors to ensure compliance with Dillard's Social Accountability Policy.
  2. Conducts audits of suppliers of products imported by Dillard's to evaluate supplier compliance with company standards for trafficking and slavery in supply chains. See [Dillard's Social Accountability Policy](https://investor.shareholder.com/dillards/documentdisplay.cfm?DocumentID=3150) and [Dillard's Social Accountability Report](https://investor.shareholder.com/dillards/documentdisplay.cfm?DocumentID=6458) for details.
  3. Requires direct suppliers to certify that materials incorporated into the product comply with the laws regarding slavery and human trafficking of the country or countries in which they are doing business. See [Dillard's Social Accountability Policy](https://investor.shareholder.com/dillards/documentdisplay.cfm?DocumentID=3150) which is applicable to import vendors. Dillard's requires all vendors, pursuant to its purchase order terms, to warrant, represent and agree that all merchandise shipped to Dillard's was manufactured and produced in full compliance with any applicable current, or later adopted, laws of the country of manufacturer governing the use of child labor, illegal forced labor, illegal prison labor or similar illegal working conditions, as well as any other applicable human rights statutes, regulations and laws.
  4. Maintains internal accountability standards and procedures for employees or contractors failing to meet company standards regarding slavery and human trafficking for imported products. See [Dillard's Social Accountability Policy](https://investor.shareholder.com/dillards/documentdisplay.cfm?DocumentID=3150) and [Dillard's Social Accountability Report](https://investor.shareholder.com/dillards/documentdisplay.cfm?DocumentID=6458) for details.
  5. Provides company employees and management, who have direct responsibility for import supply chain management, training on human trafficking and slavery, risks within the supply chains of products. See [Dillard's Social Accountability Policy](https://investor.shareholder.com/dillards/documentdisplay.cfm?DocumentID=3150) and [Dillard's Social Accountability Report](https://investor.shareholder.com/dillards/documentdisplay.cfm?DocumentID=6458) for details.

### 

Copyright Notice

The entire contents of this site are the sole and exclusive property of Dillard's, Inc. and are subject to United States and worldwide laws and treaties restricting the copy, distribution, publishing and transmission of same. No portion of this site may be copied, distributed, published or transmitted without the express written consent of Dillard's, Inc. Users of this site may download and print materials from this site for personal, non-commercial use related to placement of an order or shopping with Dillard's, provided that any such copy must contain this notice.

All of this web site's content and supporting code are copyrighted by or licensed to Dillard's, Inc. and all rights are reserved. All content copies, either electronic or printed, are for personal use only. The content and supporting code contained herein may not be used in any other manner unless express written permission is obtained in advance.

### Dillards.com Privacy Policy

Dillard's understands that online and mobile privacy is very important to you. We have adopted this Privacy Policy as part of our commitment to your privacy. The terms "we", "us", and "our" refer to Dillard's Inc. and its affiliated companies.

This Privacy Policy applies to information we obtain via Dillards.com (referred to hereafter as the Site). Please note that the Privacy Policy applies only to your interactions with us through the Site. It does not apply to interactions through our retail stores, or to your use of a Dillard's Card. A separate Privacy Notice, administered by Wells Fargo Bank, N.A., pertains to your Dillard's Credit Card and Dillard's American Express® Card. For that Privacy Notice, [click here](https://retailservices.wellsfargo.com/pdf/dillards/privacy.pdf). When you use your Dillard's Credit Card or Dillard's American Express® Card on the Site, this Privacy Notice fully applies to your usage of the Site. Additionally, when using the Site you may submit product reviews. We currently use a company called PowerReviews for product reviews. Your submission of reviews is governed by a separate privacy policy maintained by PowerReviews. A link to that policy is provided on the screen from which you submit your review, but you can also review it [here](https://www.powerreviews.com/privacy-policy/). Also, if you click the [Dillard's Careers](https://careers.dillards.com/Careers/) link on the bottom of any Dillards.com page to search for Dillard's jobs, you will be directed to job listings on the Dillard's Career web site (careers.dillards.com). Your submission of information and the collection of information from you through the use of the [Dillard's Career web site](https://careers.dillards.com/Careers/) is governed by the privacy policy of Dillards.com.

1\. What information We Obtain

When you use the Site, we may obtain personally identifiable information from you which you give us -- such as your name, physical address, email address, telephone number, account number - as well as any information you may submit through product reviews, the Feedback function, or email. We may also collect personally identifiable information about you from third parties, such as demographic or marketing firms to improve our marketing efforts, or fraud prevention companies. Additionally, when you use the Site, we obtain information automatically, such as the Internet Protocol (IP) address and other information about the device you are using to access the Site, including browser information, Internet Service Provider (ISP), operating system, and your location.

2\. How We Use Information We Obtain

We use the information we obtain from your use of the Site to conduct our business and to market products and services to you. If you order from the Site, we may send you emails and notices about your order and about other merchandise and services that we think may be of interest to you. We may also share information we obtain with other members of the Dillard's corporate family. We do not sell or rent the information we obtain. If you want to opt out of getting promotional emails from Dillard's, see Section 5 below. We also use the information we obtain for other business purposes, such as payment processing, analytics, fraud prevention, and legal compliance.

3\. How We Share Information We Obtain

We may disclose the information we obtain with service providers that perform marketing, promotional and other services for us. Service providers who perform marketing services on our behalf are required by us to use personally identifiable information we share only to help us to provide you with products and services from Dillard's. We may also provide information to carefully selected outside companies for the purpose of jointly marketing a product or service to you. We may share information about aggregate shopping histories and demographics with consultants and others for purposes such as analyzing sales, website performance, retail trends and marketing, but such information does not identify you or any other individual.

We also share information with other companies which provide us with services we use to conduct our business operations, including product recommendations and fraud prevention. We may also share information when we believe that it is required by law or necessary to operate our business (e.g., to our attorneys, auditors, or accountants), to protect your rights, to protect our rights, or to protect the rights of others. We may also disclose the information we obtain to any company which may in the future acquire Dillard's or a portion of its business.

4\. How We Use Cookies and Similar Technology

A "cookie" is a small data file stored by your web browser on your device. It allows the Site to recognize your device upon entering the Site. We use cookies to keep track of when you return to the Site, to identify the pages you click on during your visit to the Site, and the name of the site you visited immediately before visiting the Site. We use information obtained via cookies to improve and secure the Site, including improving our site design, product assortments, customer service, and special promotions; to prevent fraud; and to provide you with product recommendations. Such recommendations may be presented to you on other sites you visit, including social network sites such as Facebook. You can disable and delete cookies through your web browser. **_However, you will not be able to make purchases on the Site if you disable cookies._**

We use Google Analytics to compile information collected via cookies in a manner which is helpful to us in analyzing visitors' use of the Site. Google Analytics also uses this information to place advertisements for our products on other sites that you visit after your use of the Site. These advertisements may be based upon the pages you visited during your use of the Site. You may opt out of Google Analytics' use of your browsing history information in this manner at any time by visiting Google's [Ad Preferences Manager](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated) You may also choose to install the [Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/), which if installed will prevent Google Analytics from using information obtained from your use of the Site.

For payment fraud prevention purposes, we use a technology called "Flash Cookies." A Flash Cookie is a data file placed on your device using Adobe Flash technology that may be installed on your computer or downloaded by you to your computer. Flash cookies are not deleted from your browser when you delete cookies through your browser's delete cookies function, and are not disabled by disabling cookies through your browser's disable cookies function. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash Cookies, [click here](https://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html). Additionally, for payment fraud prevention purposes we use a technology called HTML5 local storage technology. HTML 5 web storage is similar to a cookie in that it stores data on your device's web browser for collection of information. HTML5 local storage on your device may not in all cases be deleted or disabled by deleting or disabling cookies through your browser's delete and disable cookies functions.

5\. How You Can Opt Out of Promotional Emails

You may access and update your Personal Information and your preferences about receiving promotional emails from Dillard's at any time. To do that:

 **For Desktop Users on Dillards.com:**

  1. Click "Login" at the top of the web page
  2. Enter Email Address, Password, and Security code, then click Login 
  3. Click My Personal Information
  4. Uncheck the box for "Send me emails about store specials." Please allow up to ten days for us to process your request.

 **For Mobile/Tablet Users on Dillards.com:**

  1. Select "Login"
  2. Enter Email Address, Password, and Security code, then select Login 
  3. Select My Personal Information
  4. Uncheck the box for "Send me emails about store specials"
  5. Select "Submit"

If you "opt out" of receiving promotional emails from us, the only emails you will receive will be (I) about transactions that you initiate (such as to confirm orders you submit on the Site, inform you about your order status, respond to your customer service inquiries and answer any other questions you send us); (II) about matters affecting your Personal Information; and (III) in connection with certain services or promotions for which you have registered, such as our gift registry program.

6\. Miscellaneous Information

Changes to this Privacy Policy: We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy, and to apply any changes to previously collected personal information. We urge you to periodically check this Privacy Policy for any changes. The last revised date will change when we make revisions to the policy. All changes will be effective upon posting or as otherwise stated in the revision. If you cannot accept the terms of the Privacy Policy, as posted, please do not use the Site.

Do Not Track Header: Some web browsers and devices permit you to broadcast a preference that you not be "tracked" online. At this time we do not modify your experience based upon whether such a signal is broadcast. Data Security: Security of your information is very important to us, and we follow reasonable procedures to protect the information in our possession. However, no security system is perfect, and we accordingly cannot guarantee that a security breach will not occur.

Governing Law, Dispute Jurisdiction: The laws of the State of Arkansas, excluding its choice of law principles, govern all matters arising from or related to the Site, including your access and use, and any Internet transaction between you and us.

Links: Our Site may have links to third party websites. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any other web sites. You should review their privacy policies.

Children's Privacy: We do not knowingly request or collect personal information from any person under 13 years of age through the Site without prior verifiable parental consent. If we become aware that an individual is under the age of 13 and has submitted any information to us through the Site for any purpose without prior verifiable parental consent, we will delete his or her information from our files. Although we permit users to post reviews concerning our products, we do not encourage users to include their full name when posting reviews. If you are under 18, have included your name in a review, and would like Dillard's to remove your name you can contact us at the email address, telephone number, or mailing address below with your request. Please note that even when we remove your name, the removal may not remove the remainder of your post or remove your name from all copies of the post.

Questions?

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Policy please contact us at:

   **Dillard's, Inc.**

   Attn: Legal Dept.

   1600 Cantrell Road

   Little Rock, AR 72201

   1-800-643-8274

   Or email us at: [questions@dillards.com](mailto:questions@dillards.com)

Last Revised: April 16, 2015.

### In-Store Return Policy

We trust you will be satisfied with your Dillard's purchase. However, should you decide the merchandise is not satisfactory, Dillard's return policy is set forth below.

Dillard's will issue a refund in the form and amount of the original tender paid (including sales tax) or Dillard's will issue a Merchandise Credit at the customer's choice, when each of the following conditions has been met: 1. Merchandise will be accepted for return for thirty (30) calendar days from the date of purchase, except as otherwise stated on the face of the receipt or at point of sale; and 2. The merchandise must be in its original, unused condition unless there is a manufacturer's defect; and 3. The merchandise must be accompanied by either the original Dillard's Receipt or the original Dillard's Proof of Purchase Label. Dillard's does not give Price Adjustments. Refunds for check purchases will have a ten (10) day waiting period before a cash or check refund is issued.

### Legal Notices - Terms of Use

This web site is owned and operated by Dillard's, Inc at www.dillards.com.

The material contained within this web site is periodically checked for accuracy and is presented without any warranties, either expressed or implied. Dillard's Inc. and its subsidiaries will assume no, and hereby disclaims any, responsibility for any errors or omissions of this web site's content. Dillard's shall not be responsible for any damages incurred as a result of the content or use of this web site.

By using the material at this web site, all users agree to all terms and conditions contained in this web site, which are subject to change without notice, as well as all applicable laws, and do so at their own risk. All changes to this legal notice will be posted to this web site in a timely manner.

Occasionally, orders for an item exceeding our supply are received. If we are unable to fulfill your order, you will be notified and your credit card will not be charged.

Materials contained within this web site are intended for U.S. residents. Any deliveries requested for addresses outside the U.S. are subject to refusal by Dillard's, Inc.

Any link between Dillards.com and any other web site does not constitute an endorsement of the linked site. Dillard's, Inc. does not make and hereby disclaims any warranty as to the content of any other web site linked to Dillards.com. Exercise caution when communicating or interacting with any web site.

Any questions regarding these legal notices may be directed to:

   **Dillard's Inc.**

   Legal Dept.

   1600 Cantrell Road

   Little Rock, AR 72201

### Limitation of Liability

This website and all information contained herein are provided "as is" and without warranties of any kind, express or implied. Dillard's shall not be liable for any damages whatsoever arising out of or relating to the use by any person of this site, including but not limited to direct, indirect, consequential or punitive damages, including damages to hardware or software resulting from use of this site.

### Online Return Policy

We trust you will be satisfied with your Dillard's purchase. However, should you decide the merchandise is not satisfactory, Dillard's online return policy is stated below.

The merchandise may be mailed back to us, or returned to any Dillard's location. Please leave all merchandise tags attached. Also, please note that if you choose to mail the merchandise back, you will be responsible for the shipping fees. We recommend that you insure the package and ship via a traceable method. Dillard's offers a return label you can print from your computer and attach to the return package. No refunds are given on shipping and handling charges. Personalized items and clearance items marked down 65% or more cannot be returned.

Address package to:

   **Dillard's**

   600 Carnahan Drive

   Maumelle, AR 72113

Dillard's will issue a refund in the form and amount of the original tender paid (including sales tax) or Dillard's will issue a Gift Card, at the customer's choice, when each of the following conditions has been met: 1. The merchandise must be returned within thirty (30) calendar days from the date of purchase, except as otherwise stated on the face of the packing slip or on the item's product page; and 2. The merchandise must be in its original, unused condition unless there is a manufacturer's defect; and 3. The merchandise must be accompanied by either the original Dillard's Receipt or the original Dillard's Proof of Purchase Label. (Proof of Purchase information is included on the packing slip for all Dillard's Direct orders.)

If the merchandise being returned was purchased using a credit card and we credit your account, the credit will show on the statement you receive after the issuing bank applies the credit.

If you exchange merchandise, your account will be credited for the return and a sale rung for the new merchandise.

If the merchandise being returned was purchased using a Gift Card, that card will be credited if there is a balance on it. If the balance on the card is $0.00 a new Gift Card will be issued for the return amount and mailed to you.

### Pricing Policy

Dillard's is committed to offering quality merchandise at fair, competitive prices. In most cases, the Internet prices will reflect store prices. However, there may be some exceptions. Internet sale prices expire at midnight Central time on the date displayed for the item. Prices and sales are subject to change without notice.

Dillard's does not make price adjustments.

Merchandise available through Dillards.com may not be available in all our stores.

### Shipping Policy

Our service providers are FedEx and USPS. The carrier is determined by the service available for your "ship to" location and the method of delivery (Standard, Expedited or Next Business Day) you select. Delivery times do not include processing time. Processing time for in stock items is approximately two (2) business days.

If the item is _not_ in stock, you will receive an email to notify you. When your order ships, you will receive an email that includes the name of the carrier and a tracking number. You will also receive an email when your purchase has been delivered.

Standard delivery time is two (2) to five (5) business days after shipping. Orders requesting Expedited service or Next Business Day service, and ordered prior to 12:00 pm central time, are shipped the same day (Monday through Friday). Expedited or Next Business Day orders placed on Friday after 12:00 pm central time, Saturday, Sunday or a Holiday will be shipped the following business day. You can expect delivery in two (2) business days for Expedited service and one (1) business day for Next Business Day service after shipping.

Additional charges will be applied to merchandise shipped to Alaska, Hawaii, and U.S. Territories.

Please allow two (2) to eight (8) weeks for delivery to APO/FPO addresses. However, due to restrictions at APO/FPO postal facilities, we are unable to ship oversized and/or heavy items to APO/FPO addresses. Expedited shipping and Next Business Day shipping are not available for P.O. Box, APO/FPO addresses, Alaska, Hawaii, or U.S.Territories.

Shipping charges are calculated for each address and are based on the order amount being shipped to that address.

The following charges will apply to your order:

Shipping ChargesORDER AMOUNT| STANDARD| EXPEDITED| Next Business Day  
---|---|---|---  
Up to $149.99|  $8.50 | $18.50| $28.50  
$150.00 and Up| $11.95| $21.95| $31.95  
  
Items, including certain electronics that are very large or fragile may include an additional shipping charge. Items in a multi-item order may be shipped separately and from different locations.

Gift Cards are shipped U.S. Mail at no charge for Standard delivery. There is an $8.50 charge for Expedited delivery and an $18.50 charge for Next Business Day delivery.

Dillard's does not ship fragrances, aerosols, and alcohol based products via Expedited delivery, Next Business Day delivery or to P.O. boxes, military facilities or outside the continental United States. Please select Standard delivery for the shipment of these items.

Our transit map gives the average number of business days required for delivery after shipment.

### Submission of Information to Dillard's

Dillard's shall have a permanent, irrevocable license to modify, retransmit, license, distribute, sell or otherwise use in any manner any and all information, including suggestions and ideas, submitted to Dillard's through use of this site, without any obligation to compensate or further notify the person submitting the information of such use.

Any person submitting, posting or displaying any data, text, music, sound, photographs, graphics, video, messages, tags and/or other materials ("Content"), in any media, to Dillard's, whether publicly or privately transmitted, represents, warrants and agree that she is the sole owner of such Content and has the lawful right to submit same for use by Dillard's. Further, any person submitting Content grants to Dillard's a permanent, irrevocable license to modify, retransmit, license, distribute, sell or otherwise use in any manner any and all Content submitted without any obligation to compensate or further notify the person submitting the Content of such use.

### Tax Information

Tax Information Dillard's Inc. operates in 29 states throughout the U.S. Current law requires us to collect all state taxes that are applicable, based on the order's "ship to" address. Be advised that some states require a tax on the delivery and/or gift wrap charges, as well. All applicable taxes will be clearly displayed on your order at order completion time.

NOTE: Tax rates are subject to change at any time.

ALL VERMONT PURCHASERS

This is to notify Vermont purchasers that sales or use tax may be due on any nonexempt purchases made through Dillard’s, and that the State of Vermont requires the purchaser to pay any sales or use tax due on his or her tax return.

ALL PUERTO RICO PURCHASERS

This is to notify Puerto Rico purchasers that any purchase made through Dillard’s may be subject to sales or use tax in Puerto Rico, and that purchasers should file an Import Declaration and Tax on Imports Monthly Return, and pay any sales or use tax that may be due.

ALL SOUTH DAKOTA PURCHASERS

This is to notify South Dakota purchasers that Dillard’s is not required to and does not collect South Dakota sales or use tax on any purchase made through Dillard’s. The purchase is subject to state use tax unless it is specifically exempt from taxation. The purchase is not exempt merely because the purchase is made over the Internet, by catalog, or by other remote means. The state requires each South Dakota purchaser to report and pay tax on any purchase that was not taxed. The tax may be reported and paid on the South Dakota use tax form. The use tax form and corresponding instructions are available on the South Dakota Department of Revenue and Regulation website.

ALL RHODE ISLAND PURCHASERS

This is to notify Rhode Island purchasers that sales or use tax is due on any taxable purchases made from Dillard’s. If tax was not paid at the time of purchase, the State of Rhode Island requires all customers who use, store, or otherwise consume taxable goods or services in Rhode Island to file a signed use tax return, Form T-205. This form is available on the Rhode Island Division of Taxation’s website (www.tax.ri.gov).

### 

The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act

The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) protects the online privacy and personal information of children under 13 years of age. In compliance with this act, Dillard's does not promote online to children, and does not intentionally collect any personally identifiable information from children under 13. Children under the age of 13 must be signed up by their parents and use their parents email address in order to receive email updates.

The Dillard's American Express® Card is issued and administered by Wells Fargo Bank, N.A.

This credit card program is issued and administered by Wells Fargo Bank, N.A., pursuant to a license from American Express. American Express is a federally registered service mark of American Express.

## Policies & Notices

### California Transparency in Supply Chains Act

California Transparency in Supply Chain Act Statement 2010

The following describes Dillard's efforts to eradicate slavery and human trafficking from its direct supply chains. Among other measures, Dillard's:

  1. Engages in verification of product supply chains for products imported by Dillard's to evaluate and address risks of human trafficking and slavery. See [Dillard's Social Accountability Policy](https://investor.shareholder.com/dillards/documentdisplay.cfm?DocumentID=3150) and [Dillard's Social Accountability Report](https://investor.shareholder.com/dillards/documentdisplay.cfm?DocumentID=6458) for details. Dillard's utilizes third party inspectors to ensure compliance with Dillard's Social Accountability Policy.
  2. Conducts audits of suppliers of products imported by Dillard's to evaluate supplier compliance with company standards for trafficking and slavery in supply chains. See [Dillard's Social Accountability Policy](https://investor.shareholder.com/dillards/documentdisplay.cfm?DocumentID=3150) and [Dillard's Social Accountability Report](https://investor.shareholder.com/dillards/documentdisplay.cfm?DocumentID=6458) for details.
  3. Requires direct suppliers to certify that materials incorporated into the product comply with the laws regarding slavery and human trafficking of the country or countries in which they are doing business. See [Dillard's Social Accountability Policy](https://investor.shareholder.com/dillards/documentdisplay.cfm?DocumentID=3150) which is applicable to import vendors. Dillard's requires all vendors, pursuant to its purchase order terms, to warrant, represent and agree that all merchandise shipped to Dillard's was manufactured and produced in full compliance with any applicable current, or later adopted, laws of the country of manufacturer governing the use of child labor, illegal forced labor, illegal prison labor or similar illegal working conditions, as well as any other applicable human rights statutes, regulations and laws.
  4. Maintains internal accountability standards and procedures for employees or contractors failing to meet company standards regarding slavery and human trafficking for imported products. See [Dillard's Social Accountability Policy](https://investor.shareholder.com/dillards/documentdisplay.cfm?DocumentID=3150) and [Dillard's Social Accountability Report](https://investor.shareholder.com/dillards/documentdisplay.cfm?DocumentID=6458) for details.
  5. Provides company employees and management, who have direct responsibility for import supply chain management, training on human trafficking and slavery, risks within the supply chains of products. See [Dillard's Social Accountability Policy](https://investor.shareholder.com/dillards/documentdisplay.cfm?DocumentID=3150) and [Dillard's Social Accountability Report](https://investor.shareholder.com/dillards/documentdisplay.cfm?DocumentID=6458) for details.

### 

Copyright Notice

The entire contents of this site are the sole and exclusive property of Dillard's, Inc. and are subject to United States and worldwide laws and treaties restricting the copy, distribution, publishing and transmission of same. No portion of this site may be copied, distributed, published or transmitted without the express written consent of Dillard's, Inc. Users of this site may download and print materials from this site for personal, non-commercial use related to placement of an order or shopping with Dillard's, provided that any such copy must contain this notice.

All of this web site's content and supporting code are copyrighted by or licensed to Dillard's, Inc. and all rights are reserved. All content copies, either electronic or printed, are for personal use only. The content and supporting code contained herein may not be used in any other manner unless express written permission is obtained in advance.

### Dillards.com Privacy Policy

Dillard's understands that online and mobile privacy is very important to you. We have adopted this Privacy Policy as part of our commitment to your privacy. The terms "we", "us", and "our" refer to Dillard's Inc. and its affiliated companies.

This Privacy Policy applies to information we obtain via Dillards.com (referred to hereafter as the Site). Please note that the Privacy Policy applies only to your interactions with us through the Site. It does not apply to interactions through our retail stores, or to your use of a Dillard's Card. A separate Privacy Notice, administered by Wells Fargo Bank, N.A., pertains to your Dillard's Credit Card and Dillard's American Express® Card. For that Privacy Notice, [click here](https://retailservices.wellsfargo.com/pdf/dillards/privacy.pdf). When you use your Dillard's Credit Card or Dillard's American Express® Card on the Site, this Privacy Notice fully applies to your usage of the Site. Additionally, when using the Site you may submit product reviews. We currently use a company called PowerReviews for product reviews. Your submission of reviews is governed by a separate privacy policy maintained by PowerReviews. A link to that policy is provided on the screen from which you submit your review, but you can also review it [here](https://www.powerreviews.com/privacy-policy/). Also, if you click the [Dillard's Careers](https://careers.dillards.com/Careers/) link on the bottom of any Dillards.com page to search for Dillard's jobs, you will be directed to job listings on the Dillard's Career web site (careers.dillards.com). Your submission of information and the collection of information from you through the use of the [Dillard's Career web site](https://careers.dillards.com/Careers/) is governed by the privacy policy of Dillards.com.

1\. What information We Obtain

When you use the Site, we may obtain personally identifiable information from you which you give us -- such as your name, physical address, email address, telephone number, account number - as well as any information you may submit through product reviews, the Feedback function, or email. We may also collect personally identifiable information about you from third parties, such as demographic or marketing firms to improve our marketing efforts, or fraud prevention companies. Additionally, when you use the Site, we obtain information automatically, such as the Internet Protocol (IP) address and other information about the device you are using to access the Site, including browser information, Internet Service Provider (ISP), operating system, and your location.

2\. How We Use Information We Obtain

We use the information we obtain from your use of the Site to conduct our business and to market products and services to you. If you order from the Site, we may send you emails and notices about your order and about other merchandise and services that we think may be of interest to you. We may also share information we obtain with other members of the Dillard's corporate family. We do not sell or rent the information we obtain. If you want to opt out of getting promotional emails from Dillard's, see Section 5 below. We also use the information we obtain for other business purposes, such as payment processing, analytics, fraud prevention, and legal compliance.

3\. How We Share Information We Obtain

We may disclose the information we obtain with service providers that perform marketing, promotional and other services for us. Service providers who perform marketing services on our behalf are required by us to use personally identifiable information we share only to help us to provide you with products and services from Dillard's. We may also provide information to carefully selected outside companies for the purpose of jointly marketing a product or service to you. We may share information about aggregate shopping histories and demographics with consultants and others for purposes such as analyzing sales, website performance, retail trends and marketing, but such information does not identify you or any other individual.

We also share information with other companies which provide us with services we use to conduct our business operations, including product recommendations and fraud prevention. We may also share information when we believe that it is required by law or necessary to operate our business (e.g., to our attorneys, auditors, or accountants), to protect your rights, to protect our rights, or to protect the rights of others. We may also disclose the information we obtain to any company which may in the future acquire Dillard's or a portion of its business.

4\. How We Use Cookies and Similar Technology

A "cookie" is a small data file stored by your web browser on your device. It allows the Site to recognize your device upon entering the Site. We use cookies to keep track of when you return to the Site, to identify the pages you click on during your visit to the Site, and the name of the site you visited immediately before visiting the Site. We use information obtained via cookies to improve and secure the Site, including improving our site design, product assortments, customer service, and special promotions; to prevent fraud; and to provide you with product recommendations. Such recommendations may be presented to you on other sites you visit, including social network sites such as Facebook. You can disable and delete cookies through your web browser. **_However, you will not be able to make purchases on the Site if you disable cookies._**

We use Google Analytics to compile information collected via cookies in a manner which is helpful to us in analyzing visitors' use of the Site. Google Analytics also uses this information to place advertisements for our products on other sites that you visit after your use of the Site. These advertisements may be based upon the pages you visited during your use of the Site. You may opt out of Google Analytics' use of your browsing history information in this manner at any time by visiting Google's [Ad Preferences Manager](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated) You may also choose to install the [Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/), which if installed will prevent Google Analytics from using information obtained from your use of the Site.

For payment fraud prevention purposes, we use a technology called "Flash Cookies." A Flash Cookie is a data file placed on your device using Adobe Flash technology that may be installed on your computer or downloaded by you to your computer. Flash cookies are not deleted from your browser when you delete cookies through your browser's delete cookies function, and are not disabled by disabling cookies through your browser's disable cookies function. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash Cookies, [click here](https://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html). Additionally, for payment fraud prevention purposes we use a technology called HTML5 local storage technology. HTML5 web storage is similar to a cookie in that it stores data on your device's web browser for collection of information. HTML5 local storage on your device may not in all cases be deleted or disabled by deleting or disabling cookies through your browser's delete and disable cookies functions.

5\. How You Can Opt Out of Promotional Emails

You may access and update your Personal Information and your preferences about receiving promotional emails from Dillard's at any time. To do that:

 **For Desktop/Tablet Users on Dillards.com:**

  1. Enter your email address into the email field at the bottom of the page
  2. Uncheck the box that opts you IN to the promotional emails and click Submit

If you "opt out" of receiving promotional emails from us, the only emails you will receive will be (I) about transactions that you initiate (such as to confirm orders you submit on the Site, inform you about your order status, respond to your customer service inquiries and answer any other questions you send us); (II) about matters affecting your Personal Information; and (III) in connection with certain services or promotions for which you have registered, such as our gift registry program.

6\. Miscellaneous Information

Changes to this Privacy Policy: We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy, and to apply any changes to previously collected personal information. We urge you to periodically check this Privacy Policy for any changes. The last revised date will change when we make revisions to the policy. All changes will be effective upon posting or as otherwise stated in the revision. If you cannot accept the terms of the Privacy Policy, as posted, please do not use the Site.

Do Not Track Header: Some web browsers and devices permit you to broadcast a preference that you not be "tracked" online. At this time we do not modify your experience based upon whether such a signal is broadcast. Data Security: Security of your information is very important to us, and we follow reasonable procedures to protect the information in our possession. However, no security system is perfect, and we accordingly cannot guarantee that a security breach will not occur.

Governing Law, Dispute Jurisdiction: The laws of the State of Arkansas, excluding its choice of law principles, govern all matters arising from or related to the Site, including your access and use, and any Internet transaction between you and us.

Links: Our Site may have links to third party websites. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any other web sites. You should review their privacy policies.

Children's Privacy: We do not knowingly request or collect personal information from any person under 13 years of age through the Site without prior verifiable parental consent. If we become aware that an individual is under the age of 13 and has submitted any information to us through the Site for any purpose without prior verifiable parental consent, we will delete his or her information from our files. Although we permit users to post reviews concerning our products, we do not encourage users to include their full name when posting reviews. If you are under 18, have included your name in a review, and would like Dillard's to remove your name you can contact us at the email address, telephone number, or mailing address below with your request. Please note that even when we remove your name, the removal may not remove the remainder of your post or remove your name from all copies of the post.

Questions?

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Policy please contact us at:

   **Dillard's, Inc.**

   Attn: Legal Dept.

   1600 Cantrell Road

   Little Rock, AR 72201

   1-800-643-8274

   Or email us at: [internationalsales@dillards.com](mailto:internationalsales@dillards.com)

Last Revised: April 16, 2015.

### Legal Notices - Terms of Use

This web site is owned and operated by Dillard's, Inc at www.dillards.com.

The material contained within this web site is periodically checked for accuracy and is presented without any warranties, either expressed or implied. Dillard's Inc. and its subsidiaries will assume no, and hereby disclaims any, responsibility for any errors or omissions of this web site's content. Dillard's shall not be responsible for any damages incurred as a result of the content or use of this web site.

By using the material at this web site, all users agree to all terms and conditions contained in this web site, which are subject to change without notice, as well as all applicable laws, and do so at their own risk. All changes to this legal notice will be posted to this web site in a timely manner.

Occasionally, orders for an item exceeding our supply are received. If we are unable to fulfill your order, you will be notified and your credit card will not be charged.

Materials contained within this web site are intended for U.S. residents. Any deliveries requested for addresses outside the U.S. are subject to refusal by Dillard's, Inc.

Any link between Dillards.com and any other web site does not constitute an endorsement of the linked site. Dillard's, Inc. does not make and hereby disclaims any warranty as to the content of any other web site linked to Dillards.com. Exercise caution when communicating or interacting with any web site.

Any questions regarding these legal notices may be directed to:

   **Dillard's Inc.**

   Attn: Legal Dept.

   1600 Cantrell Road

   Little Rock, AR 72201

### Limitation of Liability

This website and all information contained herein are provided "as is" and without warranties of any kind, express or implied. Dillard's shall not be liable for any damages whatsoever arising out of or relating to the use by any person of this site, including but not limited to direct, indirect, consequential or punitive damages, including damages to hardware or software resulting from use of this site.

### Pricing Policy

Dillard's is committed to offering quality merchandise at fair, competitive prices. In most cases, the Internet prices will reflect store prices. However, there may be some exceptions. Internet sale prices expire at midnight Central time on the date displayed for the item. Prices and sales are subject to change without notice.

Dillard's does not make price adjustments.

Merchandise available through Dillards.com may not be available in all our stores.

### Security

We are committed to maintaining the security of the information we receive from you. To prevent unauthorized access, we have implemented appropriate software and management procedures which we monitor continuously. Encryption is a process which scrambles your personal information while it is in transit to us. We encrypt sensitive information as you key it in your browser via a "secure socket layer", or SSL, which is the industry standard for encrypting transmitted data. Upon receipt, your information is stored on a secured server behind a firewall. This secured server is not directly connected to the Internet, and the firewall which protects it meets all industry standards. In addition, the facility that houses the server is physically secured to further protect your information against loss, alteration or misuse. We are and will continue to be diligent in our efforts to ensure that your personal information is secure with us.

### Tax Information

Tax Information Dillard's Inc. operates in 29 states throughout the U.S. Current law requires us to collect all state taxes that are applicable, based on the order's "ship to" address. Be advised that some states require a tax on the delivery and/or gift wrap charges, as well. All applicable taxes will be clearly displayed on your order at order completion time.

NOTE: Tax rates are subject to change at any time.

ALL VERMONT PURCHASERS

This is to notify Vermont purchasers that sales or use tax may be due on any nonexempt purchases made through Dillard’s, and that the State of Vermont requires the purchaser to pay any sales or use tax due on his or her tax return.

ALL PUERTO RICO PURCHASERS

This is to notify Puerto Rico purchasers that any purchase made through Dillard’s may be subject to sales or use tax in Puerto Rico, and that purchasers should file an Import Declaration and Tax on Imports Monthly Return, and pay any sales or use tax that may be due.

ALL SOUTH DAKOTA PURCHASERS

This is to notify South Dakota purchasers that Dillard’s is not required to and does not collect South Dakota sales or use tax on any purchase made through Dillard’s. The purchase is subject to state use tax unless it is specifically exempt from taxation. The purchase is not exempt merely because the purchase is made over the Internet, by catalog, or by other remote means. The state requires each South Dakota purchaser to report and pay tax on any purchase that was not taxed. The tax may be reported and paid on the South Dakota use tax form. The use tax form and corresponding instructions are available on the South Dakota Department of Revenue and Regulation website.

ALL RHODE ISLAND PURCHASERS

This is to notify Rhode Island purchasers that sales or use tax is due on any taxable purchases made from Dillard’s. If tax was not paid at the time of purchase, the State of Rhode Island requires all customers who use, store, or otherwise consume taxable goods or services in Rhode Island to file a signed use tax return, Form T-205. This form is available on the Rhode Island Division of Taxation’s website (www.tax.ri.gov).

### The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act

The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) protects the online privacy and personal information of children under 13 years of age. In compliance with this act, Dillard's does not promote online to children, and does not intentionally collect any personally identifiable information from children under 13. Children under the age of 13 must be signed up by their parents and use their parents email address in order to receive email updates.

The Dillard's American Express® Card is issued and administered by Wells Fargo Bank, N.A.

This credit card program is issued and administered by Wells Fargo Bank, N.A., pursuant to a license from American Express. American Express is a federally registered service mark of American Express.
